<article>
	<introduction>
		<title>Connect to Wi-Fi on your iPhone, iPad, or iPod touch</title>
		<goal>Learn how to connect your device to a Wi-Fi network, including open, secure, and hidden networks.</goal>
		<articlenavigation>
			<sectionlink>Wi-Fi network</sectionlink>
			<sectionlink>Secure Wi-Fi network</sectionlink>
			<sectionlink>Hidden Wi-Fi network</sectionlink>
		</articlenavigation>
	</introduction>	
	<body>
		<section>
			<heading>Connect to Wi-Fi networks</heading>
			<procedure>
				<step>
					<instruction>Tap Settings > Wi-Fi, and make sure Wi-Fi is turned on. Your device will search for available Wi-Fi networks.</instruction>
					<img>image 1</img>
				</step>
				<step>
					<instruction>Tap the name of the Wi-Fi network you'd like to join.</instruction>
					<img>image 2</img>
				</step>
				<procedurenote>After you've joined the network, you should see  next to the network, and  in the upper-left side of your display.</procedurenote>
			</procedure>
		</section>
		<section>
			<heading>Connect to secure Wi-Fi networks</heading>
			<procedure>
				<step>
					<instruction>Tap Settings > Wi-Fi, and make sure Wi-Fi is turned on. Then, tap the name of the Wi-Fi network you'd like to join. Password-protected networks have   by their names.</instruction>
					<img>image 3</img>
				</step>
				<step>
					<instruction>When asked, enter the password and tap Join. If tapping Join has no effect, the password you entered is too short. </instruction>
					<img>image 4</img>
				</step>
				<procedurenote>If you don't know the password to the Wi-Fi network, contact your network administrator.</procedurenote>
				<procedurenote>After you've joined the network, you should see  next to the network, and  in the upper-left side of your display.</procedurenote>
			</procedure>
		</section>
		<section>
			<heading>Connect to hidden Wi-Fi networks</heading>
			<sectiondescription>Since hidden networks won't appear in your device's list of available networks, you'll need to know the exact name of the network you're trying to join.</sectiondescription>
			<procedure>
				<step>
					<instruction>Tap Settings > Wi-Fi, and make sure Wi-Fi is turned on. Tap Other.</instruction>
					<img>image 5</img>
				</step>
				<step>
					<instruction>Enter the exact name of the network, then tap Security.</instruction>
					<img>image 6</img>
				</step>
				<step>
					<instruction>Pick the security type. Not all hidden networks are secure. Check with the network administrator if necessary.</instruction>
					<img>image 7</img>
				</step>
				<step>
					<instruction>At the top of the screen, tap Other Network to return to the previous screen.</instruction>
				</step>
				<step>
					<instruction>Enter the network password in the Password field, then tap Join.</instruction>
					<img>image 8</img>
				</step>
				<procedurenote>After you've joined the network, you should see  next to the network, and  in the upper-left side of your display. </procedurenote>
			</procedure>
		</section>
		<learnmore>
			<related>Joining subscription Wi-Fi networks</related>
			<related>If you can't connect to a Wi-Fi network</related>
			<related>If the Wi-Fi settings are grayed out or dim</related>
			<related>About settings for Wi-Fi routers and access points</related>
		</learnmore>
	</body>
</article>